<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>OsE Santos on OsE Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OsE Santos on OsE Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.149.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:16:01 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Adventure Building a Sweep Keyboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/building_sweep_kb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:16:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/building_sweep_kb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-adventure-building-a-sweep-keyboard&#34;&gt;My Adventure Building a Sweep Keyboard&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here starts my journey as a blogger and technology enthusiast.
My love for keyboards started when I decided that I wanted a small keyboard that it could make me more productive and that I could take with me everywhere. Until then I only used the laptop keyboards and the big membrane keyboards, and it was ok for all my life however when you are a software developer sometimes a regular keyboard is not enough. You want to stand out, you want to be different, you want to be that guy that you look and thinks &amp;ldquo;wow if that guy uses that keyboard to write code then he should be the best :p&amp;rdquo;.
So I&amp;rsquo;ve stater to look for the best alternative and, I want it all, I wanted lights, I wanted mechanical switches layers upon layers, compact design but also retro look, like those old white, gray and beige keyboards that you could find in the 90s.
After some deep research I found what I thought would be a keyboard for the rest of my life, and damn I was wrong&amp;hellip; I found the Vortex core 40% keyboard, it was perfect, it had everything I wanted, it was compact, it had lights, it had mechanical switches and it was retro looking. I ordered it and waited for it to arrive.
Upon arrival I quickly realized that it would take me some time to really get the grasp of it, but it was ok. I was ready to learn, I was ready to adapt.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:25:20 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
